discoverychannel.co.uk 2019-04-14

# Privacy Policy - Discovery UK

**OVERVIEW**

 **A.     Who we are: **

We are Discovery Corporate Services Limited. We provide this website [www.discoveryuk.com](http://www.uk.tlc.com/) (the “ **Site** “) in the United Kingdom.

We are based in the United Kingdom. Our company details are in section 1 below.

If you have any questions or need any help in relation to our privacy policy, please contact our Data Protection Officer at [DPO@discovery.com](mailto:DPO@discovery.com).

 **B.     Our values and what this privacy policy is for:**

We value your privacy and want to be accountable and fair to you as well as transparent with you in the way that we collect and use your personal information.  Our overall aim is to ensure that our collection and use of personal information is appropriate to the provision of the Site to you, and is in accordance with applicable data protection laws. We also want you to know your rights in relation to your information which you can find here, in section 10.

In line with these values, this privacy policy tells you what to expect when we collect and use personal information about you.  We have tried to make it easy for you to navigate so you can find the information that is most relevant to you and our relationship with you.

We are always looking to improve the information we provide to our customers and contacts so if you have any feedback on this privacy policy, please let us know using our contact details in section 13.

 **C.     Who this privacy policy applies to: **This privacy policy applies to all users of our Site. ****

 **D.     What this privacy policy contains: **This privacy policy describes the following important topics relating to your information.

  1. Who We Are
  2. Children
  3. The Personal Information We Collect About You
  4. How We Store And Use Your Personal Information
  5. How We Share Your Personal Information And Who We Share It With
  6. International Transfers
  7. Cookies
  8. Security
  9. Data Retention
  10. Your Rights
  11. Third-Party Sites
  12. Changes To This Privacy Policy
  13. Complaints, Questions & Suggestions

 **E.      Your rights to object: **You have various rights in respect of our use of your personal information as set out in section 10. Two key rights are that you may:

1.      ask us to stop using your personal information for direct marketing purposes.  If you exercise this right, we will stop using your personal information for this purpose; and

2.      ask us to consider any valid objections which you have to our use of your personal information where we process your personal information on the basis of our, or another person’s, legitimate interest.

 **F.      What you need to do and your confirmation to us: **Please read this privacy policy carefully to understand how we handle your personal information. ****

You can find out more information in section  10.

## Who We Are

We are Discovery Corporate Services Limited, registered in England with company number 08597513 whose registered office is at Chiswick Park Building 2, 566 Chiswick High Road, London W4 5YB, United Kingdom (“ **Discovery** ”) and we are the data controller of the personal information that we collect from you.

You can contact us in relation to this privacy policy by contacting our Data Protection Officer at [DPO@discovery.com](mailto:DPO@discovery.com).

## CHILDREN

We do not and will not knowingly collect information from any unsupervised child under the age of 13.  If you are under the age of 13, you may not use the Site unless your parent or guardian has provided us with their consent for your use of this Site.

## THE PERSONAL INFORMATION WE COLLECT ABOUT YOU

 ** _Information from your online interactions_**

We collect the following information from your interaction with the Site:

●           how you access our Site and the devices that you use to access our Site.  This includes collecting unique online identifiers such as IP address, browser type and version, time zone setting and location, browser plug-in types and versions, operating system and platform and other technology on the devices you use to access this Site.

 ** _Information that you share with us_**

When you submit personal information to us through data entry fields on the Site, we collect the following information from you:

●           your name (if you’re entering a competition);

●           your e-mail address;

●           any email communications, including attachments, which you send to us.

 ** _Third parties or publicly available sources_**

We may receive personal data about you from various third parties as set out below:

●           technical data from the following parties:

o     analytics providers;

o     advertising networks; and

o     search information providers.

●           third parties that provide certain services to us within the Services, for example, facilitating and administering customer feedback forms, newsletter subscriptions and competitions;

●           identity and contact data from publicly availably sources.

## HOW WE STORE AND USE YOUR INFORMATION

We collect, store and use your personal data including your name, contact details and other information submitted to us and service usage data for our legitimate interests, so that we can:

·           make the Site available to you;

·           administer the services;

·            if you have entered into a competition on the Site, then we will use your contact details (such as e-mail address or postal address) to inform you if you have won a prize;

·           deal with your enquiries and requests (for example if you were to call customer services to ask for help and assistance then we would need to process your contact details); and

·           suggest similar products to you that you may be interested in and to understand which products appeal to our customers.

We do not believe that our storage and use of your personal information for these purposes will unduly prejudice your rights and freedoms.

Sometimes, our use of your personal information is for purposes which are ancillary to the provision of the Site and the services.  In those circumstances, we believe we have a legitimate interest in handling your personal information, and do not believe that this storage and use of your personal information will unduly prejudice your rights or freedoms.

The relevant circumstances are:

·           detecting and preventing fraud;

·           keeping our Site, products and IT systems secure;

·           ensuring that our own processes, procedures and systems are as efficient as possible;

·           analysing and enhancing the information that we collect;

·           determining the effectiveness of our promotional campaigns and advertising;

·           service and account administration requirements such as where we need to contact you for reasons related to the service (for example, where we need to send you a password reminder, to notify you about updates or amendments to our Terms of Use, [Cookie Policy](https://www.discoveryuk.com/cookie-policy "Cookie Policy") or Privacy Policy);

·           to use IP addresses and device identifiers to identify the location of users and block any unauthorised users;

·           in some very limited circumstances, we will need to handle your personal information in a certain way to comply with our legal requirements; for example, if we are asked by regulatory bodies or law enforcement agencies to share the information;

·           where you have given us your consent, contacting you by e-mail with products and services which we think may interest you; and

·           where you have opted out of our marketing or objected to receiving e-mails from us, then we need to keep records of your preferences to ensure that we do not contact you if you have asked us not to.

Where we need to collect personal data by law, or under the terms of a contract we have with you and you fail to provide that data when requested, we may not be able to perform the contract we have or are trying to enter into with you (for example, to provide you with goods or services). In this case, we may have to cancel a product or service you have with us but we will notify you if this is the case at the time.

 ** _Anonymous data_**

We collect anonymised details about visitors to our website for the purposes of aggregate statistics or reporting purposes.  However, no single individual will be identifiable from the anonymised details we collect for these purposes.

## HOW WE SHARE YOUR PERSONAL INFORMATION AND WHO WE SHARE IT WITH

We disclose information under the following circumstances:

●  **Third-party service providers** : When we share information with third-party service companies to facilitate or to provide certain services on our behalf. This will include:

o      IT infrastructure companies that facilitate our provision of the Site and the services to you, for example;

o      IT support service providers; and

o     Other third-party service providers, for the purpose of tracking our customers’ use of the Site and the services.

These companies are authorised to use your personal information only as necessary to provide these services to us.

●  **Group companies** : We may provide your personal information to our subsidiaries or affiliated companies for the purpose of processing personal information on our behalf to provide the Site and services to you. These parties are required to process such information based on our instructions and in accordance with this privacy policy. They do not have any independent right to share this information.

●  **Compliance with laws and legal proceedings** : When we respond to court orders, or legal process, or to establish or exercise our legal rights or defend against legal claims. When we believe in our sole discretion it is necessary to share information in order to investigate, prevent or take actions against illegal activities, suspected fraud, situations involving potential threats to the physical safety of any person, violations of our terms of use, or as otherwise required by law.

●  **Merger or acquisition** : When we need to transfer information about you if we are acquired by or merged with another company.  If we are involved in a merger, acquisition, or sale of all or a portion of our assets, you will be notified afterwards via e-mail and/or a prominent notice on our Site of any change in ownership or uses of your personal information, as well as any choices you may have regarding your personal information.

## INTERNATIONAL TRANSFERS

If you are located in the EU then we may transfer personal information that we collect from you to third-party data processors located in countries that are outside of the European Economic Area (“ **EEA** “) (including to the United States) or to members of our group of companies in connection with the above purposes.  Please be aware that countries which are outside the EEA may not offer the same level of data protection as the EEA, although our collection, storage and use of your personal data will continue to be governed by this privacy policy.

When transferring personal information outside the EEA, we will:

·           include the standard contractual data protection clauses approved by the European Commission for transferring personal information outside the EEA into our contracts with those third parties (these are the clauses approved under Article 46.2 of the General Data Protection Regulation (“ **GDPR** “); or

·           ensure that the country in which your personal information will be handled has been deemed “adequate” by the European Commission under Article 45 of the GDPR; or

·           (where appropriate when we are transferring your personal information to a recipient in the US) ensure that the recipient is part of the Privacy Shield which requires them to provide similar protection to any personal data shared between Europe and the US.

You can find out further information about the rules on data transfers outside the EEA, including the mechanisms that we rely upon, on the European Commission website [here](https://ec.europa.eu/info/strategy/justice-and-fundamental-rights/data-protection_en).

## COOKIES AND SIMILAR TECHNOLOGIES

Technologies such as cookies, beacons, tags and scripts are used by us and our partners, affiliates, or analytics or service providers. These technologies are used in analysing trends, administering the Site, tracking users’ movements around the Site and to gather demographic information about our user base as a whole. We receive reports based on the use of these technologies by these companies on an individual as well as aggregated basis.

We use cookies, for example, to remember users’ settings (e.g. language preference) and for authentication. Users can control the use of cookies at the individual browser level. If you reject cookies, you may still use our Site, but your ability to use some features or areas of our Site may be limited.

Please read more about how we use cookies and what information is collected using cookies in our cookie policy [here](https://www.discoveryuk.com/cookie-policy "Cookie Policy").

## SECURITY

Whilst we take appropriate technical and organisational measures to safeguard the personal information that you provide to us, no transmission over the Internet can ever be guaranteed secure.  Consequently, please note that we cannot guarantee the security of any personal information that you transfer over the Internet to us.

We are committed to protecting your personal information using appropriate technical and operational measures such as access controls that restrict and manage the ways in which your personal information is stored and handled.

## DATA RETENTION

We will retain information (including personal information) for as long as we need to use it for the reasons set out in this privacy policy and will delete it after that time except where we need to keep any personal information to comply with our legal obligations, resolve disputes, or enforce our agreements.

In some circumstances, we may anonymise your personal data (so that it can no longer be associated with you) for research or statistical purposes in which case we may use this information indefinitely without further notice to you.

## YOUR RIGHTS

You have certain rights in relation to your personal information. If you would like further information in relation to these or would like to exercise any of them, please contact us by e-mailing our Data Protection Officer at [DPO@discovery.com](mailto:DPO@discovery.com). You have the right to request that we:

·           provide access to any personal information we hold about you;

·           update any of your personal information which is out of date or incorrect;

·           delete any personal information which we are holding about you;

·           restrict the way that we process your personal information;

·           prevent the processing of your personal information for direct-marketing purposes;

·           provide your personal information to a third- party provider of services;

·           provide you with a copy of any personal information which we hold about you; or

·           consider any valid objections which you have to our use of your personal information.

We will consider all such requests and provide our response within a reasonable period (and in any event within any time period required by applicable law). Please note, however, that certain personal information may be exempt from such requests in certain circumstances.

If an exception applies, we will tell you this when responding to your request. We may request you to provide us with information necessary to confirm your identity before responding to any request you make.

## THIRD-PARTY SITES

This Site contains links to other websites operated by third parties.  Please note that this privacy policy applies only to the personal information that we collect through the Site and we cannot be responsible for personal information that third parties may collect, store and use through their website.  You should always read the privacy policy of each website you visit carefully.

## CHANGES TO THIS PRIVACY POLICY

This privacy policy was last updated on May 24, 2018.

Please check back regularly to keep informed of updates to this privacy policy. Where we make significant changes to this privacy policy, and we have your e-mail address, we will send you notification of the changes.

## COMPLAINTS, QUESTIONS AND SUGGESTIONS

We have a Privacy Office to assist with all queries regarding our processing of personal information.  Our Privacy Office can be contacted by e-mailing our Data Protection Officer at [DPO@discovery.com](mailto:DPO@discovery.com).

If you have any complaints about our Site, please contact us at:

[DPO@discovery.com](mailto:DPO@discovery.com).

In the EEA, you may also make a complaint to our supervisory body for data protection matters (the Information Commissioner’s Office in the UK) or seek a remedy through local courts if you believe your rights have been breached.

 **Annex  **

 **List of data protection authorities (EEA countries)**

You have the right to lodge a complaint with local data protection authorities in the EEA if you believe we have not complied with applicable data protection laws.

The local authority differs depending on the country.  Please see below for details of the local data protection authorities in the EEA countries in which we operate.

 **Austria**  
Österreichische Datenschutzbehörde **  
** Hohenstaufengasse 3  
1010 Wien  
Tel. +43 1 531 15 202525  
Fax +43 1 531 15 202690  
Email: [dsb@dsb.gv.at](mailto:dsb@dsb.gv.at)  
Website: <http://www.dsb.gv.at/>

 **Belgium**  
Commission de la protection de la vie privée  
Rue de la Presse 35  
1000 Bruxelles  
Tel. +32 2 274 48 00  
Fax +32 2 274 48 10  
Email: [commission@privacycommission.be](mailto:commission@privacycommission.be)  
Website: <http://www.privacycommission.be/>

 **Bulgaria**  
Commission for Personal Data Protection  
2, Prof. Tsvetan Lazarov blvd.  
Sofia 1592  
Tel. +359 2 915 3523  
Fax +359 2 915 3525  
Email: [kzld@cpdp.bg](mailto:kzld@cpdp.bg)  
Website: <http://www.cpdp.bg/>

 **Croatia**  
Croatian Personal Data Protection Agency  
Martićeva 14  
10000 Zagreb  
Tel. +385 1 4609 000  
Fax +385 1 4609 099  
Email: [azop@azop.hr](mailto:azop@azop.hr) or [info@azop.hr](mailto:info@azop.hr)  
Website: <http://www.azop.hr/>

 **Cyprus**  
Commissioner for Personal Data Protection  
1 Iasonos Street,  
1082 Nicosia  
P.O. Box 23378, CY-1682 Nicosia  
Tel. +357 22 818 456  
Fax +357 22 304 565  
Email: [jcommissioner@dataprotection.gov.cy](mailto:jcommissioner@dataprotection.gov.cy)  
Website: <http://www.dataprotection.gov.cy/>

 **Czech Republic**  
The Office for Personal Data Protection  
Urad pro ochranu osobnich udaju  
Pplk. Sochora 27  
170 00 Prague 7  
Tel. +420 234 665 111  
Fax +420 234 665 444  
Email: [posta@uoou.cz](mailto:posta@uoou.cz)  
Website: <http://www.uoou.cz/>

 **Denmark**  
Datatilsynet  
Borgergade 28, 5  
1300 Copenhagen K  
Tel. +45 33 1932 00  
Fax +45 33 19 32 18  
Email: [dt@datatilsynet.dk](mailto:dt@datatilsynet.dk)  
Website: <http://www.datatilsynet.dk/>

 **Estonia**  
Estonian Data Protection Inspectorate (Andmekaitse Inspektsioon)  
Väike-Ameerika 19  
10129 Tallinn  
Tel. +372 6274 135  
Fax +372 6274 137  
Email: [info@aki.ee](mailto:info@aki.ee)  
Website: <http://www.aki.ee/en>

 **Finland**  
Office of the Data Protection Ombudsman  
P.O. Box 315  
FIN-00181 Helsinki  
Tel. +358 10 3666 700  
Fax +358 10 3666 735  
Email: [tietosuoja@om.fi](mailto:tietosuoja@om.fi)  
Website: <http://www.tietosuoja.fi/en/>

 **France**  
Commission Nationale de l’Informatique et des Libertés – CNIL  **  
** 3 Place de Fontenoy – TSA 80715  
75334 PARIS CEDEX 07  
Tel. +33 1 53 73 22 22  
Fax +33 1 53 73 22 00  
Website: <http://www.cnil.fr/>

 **Germany**  
Die Bundesbeauftragte für den Datenschutz und die Informationsfreiheit  
Husarenstraße 30  
53117 Bonn  
Tel. +49 228 997799 0; +49 228 81995 0  
Fax +49 228 997799 550; +49 228 81995 550  
Email: [poststelle@bfdi.bund.de](mailto:poststelle@bfdi.bund.de)  
Website: <http://www.bfdi.bund.de/>

The competence for complaints is split among different data protection supervisory authorities in Germany.  
Competent authorities can be identified according to the list provided under:

<https://www.bfdi.bund.de/bfdi_wiki/index.php/Aufsichtsbeh%C3%B6rden_und_Landesdatenschutzbeauftragte>

 **Greece**  
Hellenic Data Protection Authority  
Kifisias Av. 1-3, PC 11523  
Ampelokipi Athens  
Tel. +30 210 6475 600  
Fax +30 210 6475 628  
Email: [contact@dpa.gr](mailto:contact@dpa.gr)  
Website: <http://www.dpa.gr/>

 **Hungary**  
Data Protection Commissioner of Hungary  
Szilágyi Erzsébet fasor 22/C  
H-1125 Budapest  
Tel. +36 1 3911 400  
Email: [peterfalvi.attila@naih.hu](mailto:peterfalvi.attila@naih.hu)  
Website: <http://www.naih.hu/>

 **Iceland**  
The Icelandic Data Protection Authority **  
** Rauðarárstígur 10  
105 Reykjavík  
Tel. +354-510-9600  
Email: [postur@personuvernd.is](mailto:postur@personuvernd.is)  
Website: <https://www.personuvernd.is/>

 **Ireland**  
Data Protection Commissioner  
Canal House  
Station Road  
Portarlington  
Co. Laois  
Lo-Call: 1890 25 22 31  
Tel. +353 57 868 4800  
Fax +353 57 868 4757  
Email: [info@dataprotection.ie](mailto:info@dataprotection.ie)  
Website: <http://www.dataprotection.ie/>

 **Italy**  
Garante per la protezione dei dati personali  
Piazza di Monte Citorio, 121  
00186 Roma  
Tel. +39 06 69677 1  
Fax +39 06 69677 785  
Email: [garante@garanteprivacy.it](mailto:garante@garanteprivacy.it)  
Website: <http://www.garanteprivacy.it/>

 **Latvia**  
Data State Inspectorate  
Director: Ms Signe Plumina  
Blaumana str. 11/13-15  
1011 Riga  
Tel. +371 6722 3131  
Fax +371 6722 3556  
Email: [info@dvi.gov.lv](mailto:info@dvi.gov.lv)  
Website: <http://www.dvi.gov.lv/>

 **Liechtenstein**  
Datenschutzstelle **  
** Kirchstrasse 8  
Postfach 684  
9490 Vaduz  
Tel: +423 236 60 90  
Email: [info.dss@llv.li](mailto:info.dss@llv.li)  
Website: <http://www.llv.li/#/1758/datenschutzstelle>

 **Lithuania**  
State Data Protection  
Žygimantų str. 11-6a  
011042 Vilnius  
Tel. + 370 5 279 14 45  
Fax +370 5 261 94 94  
Email: [ada@ada.lt](mailto:ada@ada.lt)  
Website: <http://www.ada.lt/>

 **Luxembourg**  
Commission Nationale pour la Protection des Données  
1, avenue du Rock’n’Roll  
L-4361 Esch-sur-Alzette  
Tel. +352 2610 60 1  
Fax +352 2610 60 29  
Email: [info@cnpd.lu](mailto:info@cnpd.lu)  
Website: <http://www.cnpd.lu/>

 **Malta**  
Office of the Data Protection Commissioner  
Data Protection Commissioner: Mr Joseph Ebejer  
2, Airways House  
High Street, Sliema SLM 1549  
Tel. +356 2328 7100  
Fax +356 2328 7198  
Email: [commissioner.dataprotection@gov.mt](mailto:commissioner.dataprotection@gov.mt)  
Website: <http://www.dataprotection.gov.mt/>

 **Netherlands**  
Autoriteit Persoonsgegevens  
Prins Clauslaan 60  
P.O. Box 93374  
2509 AJ Den Haag/The Hague  
Tel. +31 70 888 8500  
Fax +31 70 888 8501  
Email: [info@autoriteitpersoonsgegevens.nl](mailto:info@autoriteitpersoonsgegevens.nl)  
Website: <https://autoriteitpersoonsgegevens.nl/nl>

 **Norway**  
Datatilsynet **  
** Postboks 8177 Dep.  
0034 Oslo  
Tel: +47 22 39 69 00  
Email: [postkasse@datatilsynet.no](mailto:postkasse@datatilsynet.no)  
Website: <https://www.datatilsynet.no/English/>

 **Poland**  
The Bureau of the Inspector General for the Protection of Personal Data – GIODO  
ul. Stawki 2  
00-193 Warsaw  
Tel. +48 22 53 10 440  
Fax +48 22 53 10 441  
Email: [kancelaria@giodo.gov.pl](mailto:kancelaria@giodo.gov.pl) or [desiwm@giodo.gov.pl](mailto:desiwm@giodo.gov.pl)  
Website: <http://www.giodo.gov.pl/>

 **Portugal**  
Comissão Nacional de Protecção de Dados – CNPD  
R. de São. Bento, 148-3°  
1200-821 Lisboa  
Tel. +351 21 392 84 00  
Fax +351 21 397 68 32  
Email: [geral@cnpd.pt](mailto:geral@cnpd.pt)  
Website: <http://www.cnpd.pt/>

 **Romania**  
The National Supervisory Authority for Personal Data Processing  
President: Mrs Ancuţa Gianina Opre  
B-dul Magheru 28-30  
Sector 1, BUCUREŞTI  
Tel. +40 21 252 5599  
Fax +40 21 252 5757  
Email: [anspdcp@dataprotection.ro](mailto:anspdcp@dataprotection.ro)  
Website: <http://www.dataprotection.ro/>

 **Slovakia**  
Office for Personal Data Protection of the Slovak Republic  
Hraničná 12  
820 07 Bratislava 27  
Tel.: + 421 2 32 31 32 14  
Fax: + 421 2 32 31 32 34  
Email: [statny.dozor@pdp.gov.sk](mailto:statny.dozor@pdp.gov.sk)  
Website: <http://www.dataprotection.gov.sk/>

 **Slovenia**  
Information Commissioner  
Ms Mojca Prelesnik  
Zaloška 59  
1000 Ljubljana  
Tel. +386 1 230 9730  
Fax +386 1 230 9778  
Email: [gp.ip@ip-rs.si](mailto:gp.ip@ip-rs.si)  
Website: <https://www.ip-rs.si/>

 **Spain**  
Agencia de Protección de Datos  
C/Jorge Juan, 6  
28001 Madrid  
Tel. +34 91399 6200  
Fax +34 91455 5699  
Email: [internacional@agpd.es](mailto:internacional@agpd.es)  
Website: <https://www.agpd.es/>

 **Sweden**  
Datainspektionen  
Drottninggatan 29  
5th Floor  
Box 8114  
104 20 Stockholm  
Tel. +46 8 657 6100  
Fax +46 8 652 8652  
Email: [datainspektionen@datainspektionen.se](mailto:datainspektionen@datainspektionen.se)  
Website: <http://www.datainspektionen.se/>

 **UK**  
The Information Commissioner’s Office  
Water Lane, Wycliffe House  
Wilmslow  
Cheshire SK9 5AF  
Tel. +44 1625 545 745  
Email: [international.team@ico.org.uk](mailto:international.team@ico.org.uk)  
Website: [http://ico.org.uk/](https://ico.org.uk/)
